this the craziest thing I've ever heard
of in my entire life I'm about to say I
about to get
Jason they seen this jacket was like
hell
no it's a little botle of water they
gave me on the so you guys from America
xray machine was slightly out of sink
but it was due to come off your your bag
to come off and it's ended up tagging
the one behind it some of these it takes
us 2 hours to find the people
15 minutes we're
we're I stand out in the looking get the
description and it's like but you mean I
was easy to find oh jacket and this
jacket is famous I found it in a house I
bought that was owned by a giant
interesting development in the TV
graveyard the owner was actually a
[__]
giant who the [__] lived here like God
damn
it on Tik Tok it's all over literally
the
jacket million this is not how thisp
should be is the
wildest one of those jobbies yeah you're
cute let's go too much
energy